

# NGUYỄN THU UYÊN

#### SALES EXECUTIVE

As an F&B enthusiast with 4 years of experience, together with customer-relationship strengths maintained by knowledge and understanding of hospitality, I am determined in providing customer satisfaction, as well as fostering a loyal, long-term relationship between customers and the company.

Energetic, responsible, and honest, always willing to advance the best idea to achieve positive business outcomes regardless of high pressure and challenges.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### NATIONAL ECONOMICS UNIVERSITY

DEPARTMENT:

#### **TOURISM & HOSPITALITY MANAGEMENT**

Major:

**Tourism Management** 

#### **SKILLS**

Integrity

English 4 skills

Strong customer orientation

Time management

Multitasking & Flexibility

Logical thinking & Creativity

#### CONTACT



August 9, 1999



0359111575



nguyentrnthuuyen@gmail.com



Cau Giay, Ha Noi

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### CITYSMART HOTEL MANAGEMENT

### Catering Sales Executive - Signature Restaurant

March 2022 - December 2022

- Responsible for all the sales activities including introducing the menu, responding
  to client's inquiries, sales calls, meeting old and new customers; preparing
  quotations, contracts, event orders, collecting deposits and payments.
- Work closely with the kitchen and banquet service team to make sure the operation
  is absolutely met clients' standards, as well as account & purchase team to manage
  cost and profitability.
- Handle feedback and complaints from customers and help plan improve the quality of service.
- Work with the marketing team about branding and promoting the main seasonal & special products; establish new ideas to help achieve potential customers and increase restaurant revenue.

## SEN TAY HO BUFFET RESTAURANT

## Event & Wedding Sales Administrator

October 2021 - February 2022

- Assist in communication and organization of events; synthesize, compile, and modify sales department's processes, regulations, events, and forms;
- Assist in the production of correspondence, announcements, reports, spreadsheets, and general administration for sales and marketing departments.
- Manage, arrange and check the working schedule, timetable with the team in the sales department.
- Support other customer services work-related of the restaurant; take care of customers; improve customers experiences.

#### HANOI TACO BAR RESTAURANT

#### Shift manager

2018 - 2020

- Work closely with the manager to maintain & improve customer experience and satisfaction.
- Work with suppliers to reach F&B services ingredients and equipment needs.
- Processed payments, handled cash, operated a cash register maintained inventories.
- Recruit and train new staffs, as well as remaining good working spirit for present staffs to teamwork efficiently.